

# **MOHAMMAD TOTONCHY**

totonchym@gmail.com | 0426038779 | Dianella, WA 6059

## **Summary**

Excellent time management and problem-solving skills. Organized and dependable candidate successful at managing multiple priorities with a positive attitude.highly motivated self taught frontend developer with a strong passion for learning and building websites that provide a great user experience.

#### **Skills**

- Computer knowledge
- Computer skills
- Team communications
- Team support

- Shipping and Packaging
- Understanding Customer Needs
- Issue and Complaint Resolution
- Front-End Skills: HTML5, CSS

#### Experience

ITW Proline | Perth, WA Warehouse Picker 05/2022 - Current

Centrelink | Perth, WA **Customer Service Officer** 09/2021 - 11/2021

Mini World Cup | Perth, WA **Ticket Machine** 11/2019 - 12/2019

- Pulled merchandise to fulfill orders to specification.
- Assembled customer orders from stock and placed orders on pallets for shipping department.
- Picked products by matching numbers and product descriptions using voice audio headset.
- Conducted inventory transactions using scanner gun.
- Answered phone with positive attitude and asked questions to better understand customer needs.
- Delivered fast, friendly and knowledgeable service for routine questions and service complaints.
- Educated customers on special pricing opportunities and company offerings.
- Handled fast-paced customer inquiries each day to consistently meet productivity and performance targets.
- Performed duties in accordance with all applicable standards, policies and regulatory guidelines to promote safe working environment.
- Delivered exceptional level of service to each customer by listening to concerns and answering questions.
- Offered friendly and efficient service to all customers, handled challenging situations with ease.
- Worked flexible hours; night, weekend, and holiday shifts.
- Demonstrated respect, friendliness and willingness to help wherever needed.
- Developed team communications and information for meetings.
- Carried out day-day-day duties accurately and efficiently.

Hungry Jack's | MIRRABOOKA, Western Australia

#### Kitchen Hand

01/2016 - 03/2016

Reject Shop | Balcatta, WA Shelf Stocker 09/2015 - 12/2015

- Made food according to standard recipes with requested changes for customer satisfaction.
- Kept supplies in sufficient stock by assessing inventory levels and reporting lower stock items.
- Chopped vegetables, cut up fruit and prepared sauces when kitchen staff was busy.
- Restocked supplies and prepared additional ingredients during downtime for expected busy periods.
- Maintained composure and work quality while under stress.
- Maintained high personal grooming standards and uniform presentation.
- Alternated goods in inventory by observing first-in and first-out approach to keep shelves organized and properly stocked.
- Organized warehouse and stockroom areas using forklift and pallet jacks.
- Maintained well-organized restocking areas to avoid blocking aisles or creating safety hazards.
- Helped customers locate desired items and transfer oversized items to vehicles.

### **Education and Training**

EDITH COWAN UNIVERSITY **Bachelor of Science** in Cyber Security *Expected in 11/2024*